{
  "Subjects": [
    {
      "Name": "Science",
      "Courses": [
        {
          "Name": "Chemistry",
          "CardSets": [
            {
              "Name": "48 important elements",
              "Cards": [
                {
                  "Question": "H",
                  "Answer": "Hydrogen",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "He",
                  "Answer": "Helium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Li",
                  "Answer": "Lithium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Be",
                  "Answer": "Beryllium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "B",
                  "Answer": "Boron",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "C",
                  "Answer": "Carbon",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "N",
                  "Answer": "Nitrogen",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "O",
                  "Answer": "Oxygen",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "F",
                  "Answer": "Fluorine",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ne",
                  "Answer": "Neon",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Na",
                  "Answer": "Sodium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Mg",
                  "Answer": "Magnesium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Al",
                  "Answer": "Aluminium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Si",
                  "Answer": "Silicon",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "P",
                  "Answer": "Phosphorus",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "S",
                  "Answer": "Sulphur",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Cl",
                  "Answer": "Chlorine",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ar",
                  "Answer": "Argon",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "K",
                  "Answer": "Potassium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ca",
                  "Answer": "Calcium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Sc",
                  "Answer": "Scandium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ti",
                  "Answer": "Titanium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "V",
                  "Answer": "Vanadium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Cr",
                  "Answer": "Chromium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Mn",
                  "Answer": "Manganese",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Fe",
                  "Answer": "Iron",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Co",
                  "Answer": "Cobalt",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ni",
                  "Answer": "Nickel",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Cu",
                  "Answer": "Copper",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Zn",
                  "Answer": "Zinc",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ga",
                  "Answer": "Gallium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ge",
                  "Answer": "Germanium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "As",
                  "Answer": "Arsenic",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Se",
                  "Answer": "Selenium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Br",
                  "Answer": "Bromine",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Kr",
                  "Answer": "Krypton",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Sr",
                  "Answer": "Strontium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ag",
                  "Answer": "Silver",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Sn",
                  "Answer": "Tin",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Sb",
                  "Answer": "Antimony",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "I",
                  "Answer": "Iodine",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Cs",
                  "Answer": "Cesium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Ba",
                  "Answer": "Barium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Pt",
                  "Answer": "Platinum",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Au",
                  "Answer": "Gold",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Hg",
                  "Answer": "Mercury",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Pb",
                  "Answer": "Lead",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "U",
                  "Answer": "Uranium",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Name": "History",
      "Courses": [
        {
          "Name": "AP US History",
          "CardSets": [
            {
              "Name": "Presidents",
              "Cards": [
                {
                  "Question": "President 1",
                  "Answer": "George Washington 1789-1797",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 2",
                  "Answer": "John Adams 1797-1801",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 3",
                  "Answer": "Thomas Jefferson 1801-1809",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 4",
                  "Answer": "James Madison 1809-1817",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 5",
                  "Answer": "James Monroe 1817-1825",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 6",
                  "Answer": "John Quincey Adams 1825-1829",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 7",
                  "Answer": "Andrew Jackson 1829-1837",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 8",
                  "Answer": "Martin Van Buren 1837-1841",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 9",
                  "Answer": "William Henry Harrison 1841-1841",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 10",
                  "Answer": "John Tyler 1841-1845",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 11",
                  "Answer": "James Polk 1845-1849",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 12",
                  "Answer": "Zachary Taylor 1849-1850",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 13",
                  "Answer": "Millard Fillmore 1850-1853",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 14",
                  "Answer": "Franklin Pierce 1853-1857",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 15",
                  "Answer": "James Buchanan",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 16",
                  "Answer": "Abraham Lincoln 1861-1865",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 17",
                  "Answer": "Andrew Johnson 1865-1869",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 18",
                  "Answer": "Ulysses S. Grant 1869-1877",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 19",
                  "Answer": "Rutherford B. Hayes 1877-1881",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 20",
                  "Answer": "James Garfield 1881-1881",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 21",
                  "Answer": "Arthur Chester 1881-1885",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 22",
                  "Answer": "Grover Cleveland 1885-1889",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 23",
                  "Answer": "Benjamin Harrison 1889-1893",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 24",
                  "Answer": "Grover Cleveland 1893-1897",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 25",
                  "Answer": "William McKinley 1897-1901",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 26",
                  "Answer": "Theodore Roosevelt 1901-1909",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 27",
                  "Answer": "William H. Taft 1909-1913",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 28",
                  "Answer": "Woodrow Wilson 1913-1921",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 29",
                  "Answer": "Warren Harding 1921-1923",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 30",
                  "Answer": "Calvin Coolidge 1923-1929",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 31",
                  "Answer": "Herbert Hoover 1929-1933",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 32",
                  "Answer": "Franklin D. Roosevelt 1933-1945",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 33",
                  "Answer": "Harry Truman 1945-1953",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 34",
                  "Answer": "Dwight Eisenhower 1953-1961",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 35",
                  "Answer": "John F. Kennedy 1961-1963",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 36",
                  "Answer": "Lyndon Johnson 1963-1969",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 37",
                  "Answer": "Richard Nixon 1969-1974",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 38",
                  "Answer": "Gerald Ford 1974-1977",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 39",
                  "Answer": "Jimmy Carter 1977-1981",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 40",
                  "Answer": "Ronald Reagan 1981-1989",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 41",
                  "Answer": "George H.W. Bush 1989-1993",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 42",
                  "Answer": "William J. Clinton 1993-2001",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 43",
                  "Answer": "George W. Bush 2001-2009",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 44",
                  "Answer": "Barack Obama 2009-2017",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 45",
                  "Answer": "Donald Trump 2017-2021",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 46",
                  "Answer": "Joe Biden 2021-2025",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "President 47",
                  "Answer": "Donald Trump 2025-Now",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Name": "Bible",
      "Courses": [
        {
          "Name": "Old Testament",
          "CardSets": [
            {
              "Name": "Unit 2",
              "Cards": [
                {
                  "Question": "What was the name of Moses' mother?",
                  "Answer": "Jochebad",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Miriad", "Leah", "Rachel", "Potiphar", "Bithiah" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What did Pharaoh try to do to reduce the Hebrew population?",
                  "Answer": "He ordered that all Hebrew male infants be thrown into the Nile River.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "He made his guards kill any Hebrew child they saw.", "He made all Hebrew males be thrown into the Nile River.", "He made many Hebrew males leave." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What was Moses doing when God first appeared to him?",
                  "Answer": "He was shepherding his father-in-law's flock",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "He was gathering water from a well.", "He was in Pharaoh's palace.", "He was running away from Egypt." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "God first appeared to Moses as a _____",
                  "Answer": "burning bush",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "\"I AM who I AM\" means God is 3 things:",
                  "Answer": "eternal, unchanging, self-existent",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What was the first sign God showed Moses at the burning bush?",
                  "Answer": "Moses threw his staff on the ground and God turned it into a serpent.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Locusts swarmed out of the bush.", "He made the ground holy.", "He changed the color of the flame of the bush." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Because Moses was afraid to talk to Pharaoh, God ____________",
                  "Answer": "made Aaron his spokesperson",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 1",
                  "Answer": "Water to blood",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 2",
                  "Answer": "Frogs",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 3",
                  "Answer": "Gnats",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 4",
                  "Answer": "Flies",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 5",
                  "Answer": "Livestock",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 6",
                  "Answer": "Boils",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 7",
                  "Answer": "Hail",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Locusts", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 8",
                  "Answer": "Locusts",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Darkness", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 9",
                  "Answer": "Darkness",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Death of the firstborn" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Plague 10",
                  "Answer": "Death of the firstborn",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Water to blood", "Frogs", "Gnats", "Flies", "Livestock", "Boils", "Hail", "Locusts", "Darkness" ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "The purpose of the plagues was to _____",
                  "Answer": "attack the gods of Egypt",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What were the Israelites instructed to do on passover?",
                  "Answer": "Smear lamb's blood on the doorpost.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Close their door.", "Kill their firstborn.", "Light torches to clear out the darkness." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "The passover foreshadows _____",
                  "Answer": "Christ's sacrifice",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "God used a pillar of ____ in the day, and a pillar of ____ at night",
                  "Answer": "cloud, fire",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "How did the Israelites cross the Red Sea?",
                  "Answer": "Moses parts it using the power of God.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "God provided a massive boat.", "Aaron parted it using the power of God.", "They ran down the side of the Nile and went around." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "All of the Egyptian army _____ in the Red Sea",
                  "Answer": "drowned",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What 2 foods did God provide for the Israelites in the wilderness?",
                  "Answer": "manna, quail",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "How did Moses get water from the rock at Horeb?",
                  "Answer": "He struck it with his staff.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "He shouted at the rock and it opened.", "He prayed to God to split the rock.", "He asked Aaron to hit the rock with his staff." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "Who held up Moses' hands during the battle with the Amalekites?",
                  "Answer": "Aaron, Hur",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What did Jethro tell Moses he should do?",
                  "Answer": "Appoint judges so he wouldn't be over-worked.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "Watch over his sheep.", "Appoint himself as the sole communicator to God.", "Appoint judges so they could do all the hard work for him." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                },
                {
                  "Question": "The Israelites had _____ to prepare before God appeared on Mount Sinai.",
                  "Answer": "3 days",
                  "OtherOptions": [],
                  "MaxOptions": 1
                },
                {
                  "Question": "What would happen to anyone who touched the Mount of Sinai while God was there?",
                  "Answer": "They would be put to death.",
                  "OtherOptions": [ "They would ascend to heaven.", "God would bestow his power upon them.", "God would smite them." ],
                  "MaxOptions": 4
                }
              ]
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]}